Countries and holders who want to win at the expense of others.
Åsa Larsson and Jack Werner started the "Viral Reviewer".
They run the source criticism - Sweden's national team in source criticism.
Now they and Edwin Safari do "Källkoll Corona".
Russia and China, for example.
Serbian President kissed China's flag when Chinese doctors flew in.
And Russia sent the auxiliary package to Italy with "From Russia with Love".
There is more behind the sudden kindness.
With Trump as president of the United States, relations with the EU have deteriorated-
-So to the extent that Angela Merkel and Trump didn't even shook hands.
Can you shake hands?
But Sweden has different things that come into play.
Sweden has...
... perhaps the most fragile minority government.
In several countries, such as England, the political leaders have ...
They govern the majority of Parliament.
They can run over the opponents.
They cannot do the Swedish government.
Then it is that Sweden has independent offices.
-Agencies.
-Just.
The intention is that the government should not in and poke in what they do.
This is not the case in all other countries.
Each section contains educational material at Urplay.se.
Search "Källkoll Corona" and select "Pedagogical Material".